in this lesson we have discussed vliw
processors and their titanium cousins we
have learned the pros and cons of these
processors and also some of the reasons
for the titanium's high expectations and
eventual demise
this lesson concludes the first part of
my high performance computer
architecture course where we have
learned how the modern processor core
works in the next part of the course we
will learn how to get good performance
even though the main memory is really
slow and way too small to fit the
programs we want to run after that the
final part of the course is about
putting multiple processor cores
together to get even more performance
and Energy Efficiency